{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "How many parts are time signatures made up of?"
  "incorrect": [
    "1 part",
    "3 parts",
    "4 parts"
  ],
  "correct": "2 parts"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "What does the top number of a time signature show?"
  "incorrect": [
    "How many notes are in the whole piece of music",
    "The length of the music",
    "The type of note being used"
  ],
  "correct": "How many notes there are per bar"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "What does the bottom number of a time signature show?"
  "incorrect": [
    "How many notes there are per bar",
    "How many notes are in the whole piece of music",
    "The length of the music"
  ],
  "correct": "The type of note being used"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "What time signature has 2 crotchet beats to a bar?"
  "incorrect": [
    "3/4",
    "4/4",
    "5/4"
  ],
  "correct": "2/4"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "What time signature has 3 crotchet beats to a bar?"
  "incorrect": [
    "2/4",
    "4/4",
    "5/4"
  ],
  "correct": "3/4"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "What time signature has 4 crotchet beats to a bar?"
  "incorrect": [
    "2/4",
    "3/4",
    "5/4"
  ],
  "correct": "4/4"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "How many crotchet beats are there in 2/4 per bar?"
  "incorrect": [
    "3 crotchets",
    "4 crotchets",
    "5 crotchets"
  ],
  "correct": "2 crotchets"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "How many crotchet beats are there in 3/4 per bar?"
  "incorrect": [
    "2 crotchets",
    "4 crotchets",
    "5 crotchets"
  ],
  "correct": "3 crotchets"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "How many crotchet beats are there in 4/4 per bar?"
  "incorrect": [
    "2 crotchets",
    "3 crotchets",
    "5 crotchets"
  ],
  "correct": "4 crotchets"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "How many crotchet beats are there in common time per bar?"
  "incorrect": [
    "2 crotchets",
    "3 crotchets",
    "5 crotchets"
  ],
  "correct": "4 crotchets"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "How can you represent 4/4 with a letter?"
  "incorrect": [
    "Capital A",
    "Capital B",
    "Capital F"
  ],
  "correct": "Capital C"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "What time signature can be represented by a capital C?"
  "incorrect": [
    "2/4",
    "3/4",
    "5/4"
  ],
  "correct": "4/4"
}

{
  "grade": 1,
  "category": "timeSignatures",
  "question": "What time signature is also known as common time?"
  "incorrect": [
    "2/4",
    "3/4",
    "5/4"
  ],
  "correct": "4/4"
}
